geekpedia.com 2008-06-19

# Geekpedia • Privacy Policy

This privacy statement is here to attest our commitment to privacy. The privacy policy shows you how your personal information is used. 

**IP address**  
We store your IP address (which doesn't reveal anything personal about you) in logs for security reasons and statistics. By checking your IP address we can see from what country you accesed the website, for example. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are files stored on your computer with information about websites you have visited. We store a cookie named 'Geekpedia' on your computer if you are a registered member of Geekpedia. This eases your login process, because you don't have to login everytime you visit this website. When you logout the cookie is deleted. The cookie doesn't store any personal information. 

**Member information**  
When you register with Geekpedia you must enter your first name, surname, birthday, email and other information. This information is only made public on this website, and it is not sold or disclosed to any third party. When you post something on the website like a programming tutorial, your name will be used to represent the author of that tutorial. 

**Email address**  
We don't sell your email address. Your email address is kept only in our database when you register, for contact information. It is made public only on our website, for others to contact you. It is protected by spam by using some simple ways to trick the crawlers. We will contact you only when necessary (reseting your password, tutorial approval, etc.).  
We may only send you very few emails (two or three a year) that we think you would be interested in (IT conferences, for example) and that don't have any comercial interest.  
For more information read the FAQ. 

**Security**  
This website has security measures meant to prevent loss or alteration of the information. Although we can't guaranty that the information you posted will not be alterated or deleted from our website. Backups are usually made daily. 

**Your consent**  
By using our website you understand and agree with the information displayed above.
